<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Work on Rabbit Hole | MillerApps</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/categories/work/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Work on Rabbit Hole | MillerApps</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 02:11:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//localhost:1313/categories/work/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The return</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/post/2023/2023-12-17-return/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 02:11:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/post/2023/2023-12-17-return/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Seven years have passed since I last engaged with this site and shared content. This platform remains a personal space where I post items that pique my interest or prove useful to me. During my hiatus, I ventured into construction, building and working with concrete. Before that, I had a stint in the oil fields, and even earlier in 2018, I contributed to an open-source project called Trust Wallet, which Binance eventually acquired.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;Seven years have passed since I last engaged with this site and shared content. This platform remains a personal space where I post items that pique my interest or prove useful to me. During my hiatus, I ventured into construction, building and working with concrete. Before that, I had a stint in the oil fields, and even earlier in 2018, I contributed to an open-source project called Trust Wallet, which Binance eventually acquired.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After my final contribution to this repository, I took a break from the digital world, setting aside Xcode, VS Code, and GitHub. Around the same time, my trusty 2012 MacBook Pro 15&amp;quot; ceased to receive software updates, marking the end of an era.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, I&amp;rsquo;m turning over a new leaf. Armed with a 14&amp;quot; MacBook Pro equipped with an M3 Pro chip and 36 GB of RAM, I am ready to rekindle my technical skills. My goal is to commit to creating apps, tools, and anything that I find intriguing or practical. It&amp;rsquo;s going to be a challenging journey, as I feel somewhat out of touch with the coding world. It&amp;rsquo;s almost as if I&amp;rsquo;m starting from scratch. Nevertheless, I&amp;rsquo;m ready for this long haul and excited about these new beginnings. Wish me luck on this fresh endeavor.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
