<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Focus on Rabbit Hole | MillerApps</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/categories/focus/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Focus on Rabbit Hole | MillerApps</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//localhost:1313/categories/focus/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Motivation</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/post/2024/2024-03-18-motivation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/post/2024/2024-03-18-motivation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;struggling-with-motivation-a-personal-journey&#34;&gt;Struggling with Motivation: A Personal Journey&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The struggle for motivation is perhaps universal, but for me, it rings particularly true. Whether in my personal interests, such as gaming and watching movies, or in my professional pursuits, such as software development, maintaining focus has always been a challenge. This difficulty, I suspect, might be a consequence of untreated childhood ADHD.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At 30 years old, I find my ability to persevere through tasks dwindling. Even things I deeply enjoy seem to lose my interest rapidly. As time goes on, this challenge appears to grow stronger. As I&amp;rsquo;m typing this, a part of me is already contemplating abandoning the task, forgetting that it was ever started. Ironic in a post that&amp;rsquo;s about lack of motivation, isn&amp;rsquo;t it?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <content>&lt;h2 id=&#34;struggling-with-motivation-a-personal-journey&#34;&gt;Struggling with Motivation: A Personal Journey&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The struggle for motivation is perhaps universal, but for me, it rings particularly true. Whether in my personal interests, such as gaming and watching movies, or in my professional pursuits, such as software development, maintaining focus has always been a challenge. This difficulty, I suspect, might be a consequence of untreated childhood ADHD.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At 30 years old, I find my ability to persevere through tasks dwindling. Even things I deeply enjoy seem to lose my interest rapidly. As time goes on, this challenge appears to grow stronger. As I&amp;rsquo;m typing this, a part of me is already contemplating abandoning the task, forgetting that it was ever started. Ironic in a post that&amp;rsquo;s about lack of motivation, isn&amp;rsquo;t it?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-journey-through-coding&#34;&gt;The Journey through Coding&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Software development once brought me joy and a sense of accomplishment. But those feelings became harder to sustain, leading to a hiatus of almost 8 years. Only recently, after 4 months of tentatively stepping back into the coding world, has it started to rekindle some of its initial lure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But it&amp;rsquo;s not been an easy road. For every direct pursuit of the goal, there are numerous side quests - detours into new concepts and ideas. And while these side ventures certainly add to my knowledge, they often seem like distractions from the main goal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The truth is, I don&amp;rsquo;t have a magic answer to this struggle. Could ADHD medication help? Maybe. But that&amp;rsquo;s a question for further exploration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://media3.giphy.com/media/Ri7d8I18cto2jufOKc/giphy.gif&#34; alt=&#34;Happy Rainbow GIF by Morphin&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;gaming-from-escape-to-chore&#34;&gt;Gaming: From Escape to Chore&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The world of gaming, too, has changed for me. Once a relaxing escape from reality, it now feels more like a chore. Even playing with friends often results in me merely being present, scrolling on the computer without real engagement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;seeking-solutions&#34;&gt;Seeking Solutions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Like many out there, I&amp;rsquo;m still in the process of figuring it all out. The key might be getting the right help, or perhaps it&amp;rsquo;s about finding the right routines, tactics or coping mechanisms. These are many possibilities, but as of now, I&amp;rsquo;ve yet to discover my perfect formula.
What are your experiences with this struggle? Have any tips or tactics worked particularly well for you? Feel free to share your thoughts, and let&amp;rsquo;s navigate this journey together.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
